<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Infos on Strike WEF</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/en/infos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Infos on Strike WEF</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 12:01:33 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/en/infos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Route &amp; Times</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/infos/route/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 12:01:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/infos/route/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;important-update&#34;&gt;Important Update&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The local authorities and police continue to discourage our presence on the cantonal road this year. Negotiations are ongoing, preventing us from confirming the exact route at this time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Due to the municipality&amp;rsquo;s interference, regrettably, we&amp;rsquo;ve had to make time adjustments to our plans!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;saturday&#34;&gt;Saturday&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Meeting Point: &lt;strong&gt;10:00 AM, Küblis Bahnhof&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Arrival Klosters: approx. 04:30 PM&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;sunday&#34;&gt;Sunday&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Meeting Point: &lt;strong&gt;08:00 AM, Klosters Bahnhof&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Arrival Davos: approx. 02:00 PM&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;will-you-be-taking-the-train-on-sunday&#34;&gt;Will you be taking the train on Sunday?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the rally in Davos has been brought forward, there are no early train connections to Klosters. Therefore, here are the stations where you can join us during the hike.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are we hiking against the WEF?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/infos/why/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 12:01:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/infos/why/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At the WEF, decisions are made by an elite circle that have an impact on all our lives. Even if they claim to be future-oriented, sustainable and social, one thing is at the forefront of all these decisions: their own interests. And the interests of a few super-rich people and political representatives selected by the WEF are not the interests of the general public.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-the-world-economic-forum-wef&#34;&gt;What is the World Economic Forum (WEF)?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The World Economic Forum (WEF) is a circle that operates far removed from the needs of the general population. The decisions are undemocratic, with poor and disadvantaged sections of the population in particular unable to exert any influence due to the following points.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Action Consensus</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/infos/consensus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/infos/consensus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;action-consensus-wef-hike-2024&#34;&gt;Action consensus WEF hike 2024&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To ensure that the winter hike is as safe and accessible as possible for all participants, we have drawn up an action consensus. As an action of peaceful, civil protest against the World Economic Forum (WEF), we must take care of each other and therefore want to base our actions on the following principles:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;dl&gt;&#xA;&lt;dt&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We want to have a mindful and sustainable approach to ourselves as a group of activists, which means:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/dt&gt;&#xA;&lt;dd&gt;We respect the personal boundaries of other activists.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;dd&gt;We proceed calmly and carefully and endeavour not to endanger anyone (including ourselves).&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;dd&gt;We create a regenerative culture by taking care of ourselves and each other in order to act effectively and remain sustainable.&lt;/dd&gt;&#xA;&lt;/dl&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Any form of violence is not part of our action.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antirep</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/infos/antirep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/infos/antirep/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;general-antirep-information&#34;&gt;General Antirep information:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important: The hike is authorized. In principle, you do not have to expect police contact. Nevertheless, it is important to be aware of your rights. To be on the safe side, read the following Antirep information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;general-information&#34;&gt;General information:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The only information you need to disclose about yourself is the information on your ID and your home address. Telephone/mobile phone number, place of work/employer or place of education etc. do not have to and should ideally not be disclosed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The police have the right to check your personal details. Although you are not obliged to carry an ID on you, it is advisable to take one with you when you are out and about in order to avoid trouble or lengthy investigations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Policewomen must tell you their name on request and plainclothes policewomen must show you their ID.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In the event of assaults, make a note of the names of the police officers, the place, date, time and the names and addresses of any witnesses. This is important for complaints against the police. Report assaults to the police (beatings, verbal abuse, etc.). At the end of this legal aid brochure you will find addresses where you can turn.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Write a reminder about your contact with the police as soon as possible.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;frisking--searches&#34;&gt;Frisking / searches:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Searches in public (e.g. stripping down to your underpants) are not permitted.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;However, frisking is permitted (e.g. emptying pockets, feeling for weapons).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Demand that the police search you in your car or at the police station. (You will be detained longer for this)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Only medical personnel (doctors) are allowed to search body orifices. Women* should be searched by women*, men* by men*. Although it is legally possible for men* to search women* (&amp;ldquo;in case of danger to life and limb&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;), we recommend that all women* insist on being searched by women*.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;arrest&#34;&gt;Arrest:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You must be informed of the specific charges of an arrest. Ask about the reason for your arrest and make a note of it for your memory log. The police must also observe the principle of proportionality. They can hold you for 24 hours (48 hours at weekends), after which you must be brought before a magistrate. The police will normally hold you for 1 - 6 hours.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;As a general rule, once your identity has been established, the police must let you go immediately if there is no reason for a provisional arrest and no order to produce you. And: You do not have to make any statements (eyes open, mouth shut!) and you have the right to a lawyer.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It is not you who has to prove your innocence, but the police or the investigating judge who has to prove your guilt!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;preventive-custody&#34;&gt;Preventive custody:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The police can temporarily remove you from a place or detain you if, for example, there is &amp;ldquo;reasonable suspicion&amp;rdquo; that you are a threat to public safety and order or that you are preventing or interfering with the police in their work.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Please note the following when getting a temporary arrest&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The police must immediately give you the reason for the deprivation of liberty.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You have the right to inform relatives or trusted persons as soon as possible.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You have the right to refuse to make a statement and to refuse identification measures.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The police must have a court decide as soon as possible whether you may continue to be detained.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The police must release you after 24 hours at the latest or before that if the reason for the provisional arrest no longer applies (e.g. the demonstration or football match is over, public safety and order are no longer at risk, etc.) if a court orders your release.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;refusal-to-testify&#34;&gt;Refusal to testify:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You are not obliged to make any statement!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You do not have to state: Work (employer, teacher), hobbies, acquaintances, etc. You are not obliged to give this information. Remember: This is where the interrogation begins and all statements can be used against you.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;I have nothing to say&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;I refuse to testify&amp;rdquo; are the best answers or you can simply remain silent. Shaking your head and or nodding counts as a statement.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Do not allow yourself to be intimidated or provoked. Most threats are bluffs designed to intimidate you.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Do not resist (physically), otherwise you will be liable to prosecution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you are detained at the police station for longer than 24 hours (or 48 hours at weekends), demand immediate contact with a lawyer. Legal advice hotline: 031 372 48 43 (office hours)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;identification-measures&#34;&gt;Identification measures:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Identification measures are fingers. And palm prints, photos, blood, urine and handwriting samples, etc.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packing list</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/en/infos/packinglist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/en/infos/packinglist/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-large-rucksack-with&#34;&gt;A large rucksack with:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;- Hiking boots! Good footwear is important, we will probably be walking partly through the snow&#xA;- Banners, posters&#xA;- T-shirt short and long&#xA;- Warm sweater&#xA;- Thermal underwear&#xA;- Winter jacket&#xA;- Pants, ski pants or warm trekking pants&#xA;- Underwear&#xA;- Comfortable, good and warm socks&#xA;- Nessessary&#xA;- Personal medication&#xA;- Gloves, hat, scarf&#xA;- Sun protection&#xA;- Sleeping mat&#xA;- Sleeping bag&#xA;- Headlamp&#xA;- Water bottle with water (approx. 3l) Possibly thermos flask with tea :)&#xA;- Lunch for the day of arrival&#xA;- Snacks for the hike&#xA;- Portable ashtray if you smoke&#xA;- ID/ Passport (see Anti Rep)&#xA;- approx. CHF 100 for train ticket, collection (approx. 5.- per meal)&#xA;- Tupperware with lid&#xA;- Drinking cup&#xA;- Bag for snack/bread for the break&#xA;- Thermos flask&#xA;- Cutlery&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pr</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
